82. Wind power. Around the world, people are looking for new, longer-lasting sources
of energy. One of these sources is the wind. Wind power has the potential to be an important
new way to create electricity. Wind power really is clean. Using wind turbines to generate
electricity creates no air pollution and requires no fuel. Using more wind power would actually
reduce pollution, as we would use less power from polluting sources. Besides, wind is free.
Building a turbine or mill costs money, but the wind itself costs nothing. In addition to being
free, wind is sustainable. We won't run out of wind the way we will run out of coal, oil, or other
fuel sources. In fact, the power wind can create is much greater than the world's current energy
needs, and the power can help people or small communities be self-reliant. They would rely only
on their turbine, not a city power grid. However, even wind power has some drawbacks. Some people
find wind turbines ugly. They think the turbines ruin the landscape. The turbines can also be quite
loud, which is a problem for people and animals nearby. The turbines may affect animals more than
people. They can disrupt birds' flight patterns. What's worse, they may frighten other animals away
from the area. The turbines can also cause problems with TV signals. The key to making wind power work
seems to be building more and better turbines. If we do that, it seems likely that wind power
will be more and more important in our future.